[
{"type":"header","version":"4.9.2","comment":"Export to JSON plugin for PHPMyAdmin"},
{"type":"database","name":"school"},
{"type":"table","name":"webdev","database":"school","data":
[
{"no":"1","question":"CSS was first proposed by?","answer":"Haakon Wium Lie","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"2","question":"Haakon Wium Lie introduced Css on October 10, ______.","answer":"1994","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"3","question":"he became co-author of CSS1, and is regarded as co-creator of CSS.","answer":"Bert Bos","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"4","question":"True or False SGML stands for Standard Generalized Markup Language","answer":"True","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"5","question":"True or False CSS was developed to provide style sheets for the web","answer":"True","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"6","question":"True or False One requirement for a web style sheet language was for style sheets to come from different sources on the web. ","answer":"True","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"7","question":"True or False Existing style sheet languages like DSSSL and FOSI were  suitable.","answer":"False","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"8","question":"What does DSSSL Stands for?","answer":"Document Style Semantics and Specification Language","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"9","question":"What does SGML Stands for?","answer":"Standard Generalized Markup Language","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"10","question":"Is a style sheet language for SGML and, later.","answer":"FOSI","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"11","question":"What does FOSI stands for?","answer":"Formatting Output Specification Instance","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"12","question":"_______ - was developed by the US Department of Defense to control the pagination and layout of SGML and XML technical data.","answer":"FOSI","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"13","question":"True or False FOSI style sheets are themselves written in SGML","answer":"True","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"14","question":" it is a set of instructions to a web browser on how to display various elements on a web page","answer":"Style Sheet","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"15","question":"What CSS stands for?","answer":"Cascading style Sheet\r\n","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"16","question":"___________ - Are just text files, or text embedded in the head of an html document, that help separate content from appearance.","answer":"Stylesheet","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"17","question":"True or False The content of a page goes into an HTML file. And the appearance goes into style sheet.","answer":"True","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"18","question":"it is the part of a statement which identifies page elements, normally the HTML element you want to style","answer":"selector","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"19","question":"The part of a statement which tells a browser how selected elements should be drawn\r\n","answer":"Declaration","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"20","question":"<pre style=\"color:rgb(80, 80, 80);\">\r\nh1 {\r\n   colorblue; font-size12px;\r\n}\r\n\r<\/pre>\nIn the example above, the h1 is the ____\r\n","answer":"Selector","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"21","question":"<pre style=\"color:rgb(80, 80, 80);\">\r\nh1 {\r\n  color:blue; font-size:12px;\r\n}\r\n<\/pre>\r\n\r\nIn the example above, the 'color' & 'font-style' is an example of a ____","answer":"Property","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"22","question":"CSS declarations always end with the symbol _","answer":";","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"23","question":"True or False: CSS declaration groups are surrounded by curly brackets ({})\r\n","answer":"True","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"24","question":"All Property need to have its _____","answer":"Value","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"25","question":"_______ - Loses many of the advantage of style sheets by mixing content with presentation. Use this method sparingly such as when  a style is to be applied to a single occurrence of an element.","answer":"Inline Styles","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"26","question":"______ ____ _____ - Should be used when a single document has a unique style, usually they are declared in the head section by using style tag","answer":"Internal Style Sheets","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"27","question":"______ ____ _____ - Is an ideal method when the style is applied to many pages. ","answer":"External Style Sheets","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"28","question":"An _______ ____ _____ allows changes on the look of an entire web site by changing one file. Each page must link to the style sheet using the <link> tag the browser will read the style definitions from the file ","answer":"External Style Sheets","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"29","question":"True or False: Every statement must have a selector and a declaration.","answer":"True","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"30","question":"True or False: The declaration comes immediately after the selector and contain by a pair of semicolon.\r\n","answer":"False","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"31","question":"True or False: The declaration is one or more properties separated by semicolons. ( ;)","answer":"True","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"32","question":"True or False: each property has a property name followed by a colon\r\n","answer":"True","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"33","question":"This Css property Sets all the background properties in one declaration","answer":"background","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"34","question":"This CSS Property Sets whether a background image is fixed or scrolls with the rest of the page","answer":"background-attachment","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"35","question":"This CSS property Specifies the painting area of the background","answer":"background-clip","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"36","question":"This CSS Property Sets the background color of an element","answer":"background-color","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"37","question":"This CSS Property Sets the background image for an element","answer":"background-image","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"38","question":"This CSS Property Specifies where the background image(s) is\/are positioned","answer":"background-origin","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"39","question":"This CSS Properties Sets the starting position of a background image","answer":"background-position","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"40","question":"True or False: The border-style property can have from one to four values (for the top border, right border, bottom border, and the left border)","answer":"True","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"41","question":"True or False: The border-width property can have from one to eight values","answer":"False","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"42","question":"A _________ is something that explains the relationship between the selectors.","answer":"combinator","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"43","question":"A ___ ______ can contain more than one simple selector. Between the simple selectors, we can include a combinator.","answer":"CSS selector","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"44","question":"There are four different combinators in CSS, Give all","answer":"descendant selector,child selector,adjacent sibling selector,general sibling selector","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"45","question":"The ________ ______ matches all elements that are descendants of a specified element.","answer":"descendant selector","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"46","question":"The _______ ____ selects all elements that are the children of a specified element.","answer":"child selector","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"47","question":"The ______ _____ ___ selects all elements that are the adjacent siblings of a specified element.","answer":"adjacent sibling selector","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"48","question":"The ______ ______ ____ selects all elements that are siblings of a specified element.","answer":"general sibling selector","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"49","question":"this selector is used to select the element that is the nth child, of a particular type, of its parent.","answer":":nth-of-type()","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"50","question":"________ is used in millions of Web pages to improve the design, validate forms, detect browsers, create cookies, and much more.","answer":"JavaScript","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"51","question":"is the most popular scripting language on the internet, and works in all major browsers, such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla, Firefox, Netscape, Opera.\r\n","answer":"JavaScript","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"52","question":"are used to store data","answer":"Variables","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"53","question":"is a \"container\" for information you want to store, also its value can change during the script. You can refer to a variable by name to see its value or to change its value.","answer":"Variable","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"54","question":"give all assignment operators in javascript (should be in order and separated with comma ',' )","answer":"=,+=,-=,*=,\/=,%=","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"55","question":"This symbol means equal to","answer":"==","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"56","question":"This symbol means equal to (checks for both value and type)","answer":"===","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"57","question":"Give all arithmetic operator (should be in order and separated with comma ',' )","answer":"+,-,*,\/,%,++,--","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"58","question":"Give all comparison operators (should be in order and separated with comma ',' )","answer":"==,===,!=,>,<,>=,<=","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"59","question":"Give all logical operators (should be in order and separated with comma ',' )","answer":"&&,||,!","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"60","question":"is often used if you want to make sure information comes through to the user.\r\n","answer":"Alert box","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"61","question":" is often used if you want the user to verify or accept something.\r\n","answer":"Confirm Box","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"62","question":"is often used if you want the user to input a value before entering a page.\r\n","answer":"prompt box ","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"63","question":"Give all conditional statements (should be in order and separated with comma ',' )","answer":"if, if else,if else if else","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"65","question":"What is the output of the following code:<br><br><br>\r\n<pre style=\"text-align: left; font-size:14px; color:gray; font-family:monospace\">\r\n        var x = 1;\r\n        var y = 5;\r\n        \r\n        x++;\r\n        y++;\r\n        x += ++y;\r\n \r\n        document.write(x);\r\n<\/pre>\r\n","answer":"9","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"66","question":"_______ ______ - is a block of code designed to perform a particular task","answer":"JavaScript Function","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"67","question":"A JavaScript function is executed when \"something\" _______ it or (calls it)","answer":"Invokes","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"68","question":"A JavaScript function is defined with the ______ keyword, followed by a name, followed by parentheses ().","answer":"function","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"69","question":"True or False: Function names can contain letters, digits, underscores, and dollar signs","answer":"True","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"70","question":"True or False: The parentheses may include parameter names separated by a colon:\r\n(parameter1, parameter2, ...)","answer":"False","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"71","question":"True or False: The code to be executed, by the function, is placed inside square brackets: []","answer":"False","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"72","question":"______ ______ - are listed inside the parentheses () in the function definition.","answer":"Function parameters","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"73","question":"Function ________ are the values received by the function when it is invoked.","answer":"Arguments","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"74","question":"When JavaScript reaches a _____ statement, the function will stop executing.","answer":"return ","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"75","question":"What is the output of the following code:\r\n\r\n<br><br><pre style=\"text-align: left; font-size:14px;color:gray; font-family:monospace\">\r\n\r\n        function calculateAge(birthYear,currentYear){\r\n            return currentYear - birthYear;\r\n        }\r\n\r\n        var currentYear = 2020;\r\n        var birthYear = 2000;\r\n        \r\n        var guessedAge = calculateAge(birthYear,currentYear);\r\n        document.write(guessedAge);\r\n        \r\n<\/pre>","answer":"20","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"76","question":"True or False: With a function, you can use the same code many times with different arguments, to produce different results.","answer":"True","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"77","question":"The __ Operator Invokes the Function","answer":"()","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"78","question":"True or False: Scripts cannot be placed in the body, or in the head section of an HTML page, or in both.","answer":"False","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"79","question":"Write True if the syntax is correct\r\nElse Write False\r\n\r\n<br><pre style=\"text-align: left; font-size:14px;color:gray; font-family:monospace\">\r\n         <code style=\"color:gray\"><link rel=\"stylesheet\" src=\"myScript1.js\"><code>\r\n<\/pre>","answer":"False","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"80","question":"True or False: You can place a limited amount of Script inside your HTML files","answer":"False","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"}
]
}
]
